{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "Entrepreneur",
    "Term": "First Quarter",
    "Title": "Week-4",
    "LastModified": "14 August 2025",
    "Authors": [
      "Alexander Oro"
    ],
    "References": [
      "Week-4"
    ]
  },
"quizData": [
    {
      "question": "What is the process of gathering, analyzing and interpreting the information about the products or the services to be offered for sale to the potential consumers in the market?",
      "answer": "Market Research",
      "choices": [
        "Data Collection",
        "Survey",
        "Interview",
        "Market Research"
      ],
      "reference": "Market Research and Data Collection",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the most valuable tool in any type of research study?",
      "answer": "Data Collection",
      "choices": [
        "Market Research",
        "Survey",
        "Interview",
        "Data Collection"
      ],
      "reference": "Market Research and Data Collection",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the most common way to gather primary research with the use of questionnaires or interview schedule?",
      "answer": "Surveys",
      "choices": [
        "Interview",
        "Focus Group Discussion",
        "Data Collection",
        "Surveys"
      ],
      "reference": "Data Gathering Techniques",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is one of the most reliable and credible ways of getting relevant information from target customers?",
      "answer": "Interview",
      "choices": [
        "Surveys",
        "Focus Group Discussion",
        "Data Collection",
        "Interview"
      ],
      "reference": "Data Gathering Techniques",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is typically done in person between the researcher/entrepreneur and a respondent where the researcher asks pertinent questions?",
      "answer": "Interview",
      "choices": [
        "Surveys",
        "Focus Group Discussion",
        "Data Collection",
        "Interview"
      ],
      "reference": "Data Gathering Techniques",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the traditional method of conducting an interview?",
      "answer": "Personal interviews",
      "choices": [
        "Telephone interviews",
        "Focus Group Discussion",
        "Surveys",
        "Personal interviews"
      ],
      "reference": "Data Gathering Techniques",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What allows the researcher to establish relationship with potential participants and therefore gain their cooperation?",
      "answer": "Personal interviews",
      "choices": [
        "Telephone interviews",
        "Focus Group Discussion",
        "Surveys",
        "Personal interviews"
      ],
      "reference": "Data Gathering Techniques",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What generates the highest response rates in survey research?",
      "answer": "Personal interviews",
      "choices": [
        "Telephone interviews",
        "Focus Group Discussion",
        "Surveys",
        "Personal interviews"
      ],
      "reference": "Data Gathering Techniques",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are less expensive and less time-consuming interviews?",
      "answer": "Telephone interviews",
      "choices": [
        "Personal interviews",
        "Focus Group Discussion",
        "Surveys",
        "Telephone interviews"
      ],
      "reference": "Data Gathering Techniques",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is an excellent method for generating and screening ideas and concepts?",
      "answer": "Focus Group Discussion",
      "choices": [
        "Interview",
        "Surveys",
        "Data Collection",
        "Focus Group Discussion"
      ],
      "reference": "Data Gathering Techniques",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What can be moderated group interviews and brainstorming sessions that provide information on user's needs and behaviors?",
      "answer": "Focus Group Discussion",
      "choices": [
        "Interview",
        "Surveys",
        "Data Collection",
        "Focus Group Discussion"
      ],
      "reference": "Data Gathering Techniques",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    }
  ]
}